Donald and Charlotte MacJannet Papers MS024
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Photographs and other media, 1880 -- 2000; 1915 -- 1999; MS024.007; 34.95 Linear Feet; 1 Volumes; 58 Audiovisual Object(s); 727 Digital Object(s)
  - Donald MacJannet slides from trips, home, Priory, travel, and camp, 1900 -- 1986; MS024.007.070
    - Assortment; visitors, Sweden; Geneva I; Camp; Denmark 1971-72; visitors I, Priory; Reunion 1974, 1973; MS024.007.071.00005 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - Priory; Africa; Moscow II, 1968; MS024.007.071.00006 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - Flowers; portraits; Jean; 'super'; entretien; Moscow; Ceylon, 1974; MS024.007.072.00001 (Box 72)
    - Priory; gardens and flowers; portraits; miscellaneous; Taj Mahal; Queen's silver jubilee; Cuzco, 1975; MS024.007.072.00002 (Box 72)
    - Japan, temples; Japan I; Japan, personal; Japan, Mt. Aso; Japan; Japan, palace, 1970; MS024.007.072.00003 (Box 72)
    - Girls of Japan (purchased); beauty spots of Japan (purch.); Japan; annual events of Japan (purch.); Japan, buildings; Japan amusements; Japan, workers; Japan, farm scenes; Hong Kong, 1970; MS024.007.072.00004 (Box 72)
    - unlabeled; Italy; India, Saigon, Bangkok; unlabeled; portraits; Priory; visitors, Woody, 1970; MS024.007.072.00005 (Box 72)
    - Ceylon; Delhi, Red Fort; loose slides; Angkor Wat; Angkor Wat; unlabeled; Africa, 1971; MS024.007.072.00006 (Box 72)
    - Camp (good); camp; camp (best); Region of Talloires, 1960; MS024.007.073.00001 (Box 73)
    - Paris, Geneva; Persia, Turkey; Greece; Greece; unlabeled; unlabeled; Prague; Eva, Cook, 1964 -- 1973; MS024.007.073.00002 (Box 73)
    - Japan, personal; Israel; Israel; Ethiopia, S. Africa; Tufts, Mallorca, Germany; Priory; close friends, 1970; MS024.007.073.00003 (Box 73)
    - South America; Germany; Portugal 1973; helpers; Nice, St. Jeanet, MS024.007.073.00004 (Box 73)
    - Geneva; Japan, best; Budapest; Majorca; Ilo, 1970; MS024.007.073.00005 (Box 73)
    - St. Bernart, castles; portraits of Charlotte; Madeira; Palffy, Italy; Sweden; USA 1967, Expo Montreal; flowers, MS024.007.073.00006 (Box 73)
    - Birda; Japan, garden; Japan (commercial); Japan, noh, ballet; World Youth Forum; USA; Norway, Bergen; Talloires, mountains, 1968; MS024.007.074.00001 (Box 74)
    - Munich, Oktoberfest 1960; Majorca; Sweden; travel; Zermat; Paris, MS024.007.074.00002 (Box 74)
    - Austria, Budapest; Kyoto parade; Rothenburg; portraits; unlabeled, 1972; MS024.007.074.00003 (Box 74)
    - Russia; Africa, best; Africa; Toshogu shrine; Cynthia Raymond; Copenhagen, 1973; MS024.007.074.00004 (Box 74)
    - Norway, Hamburg; India; Booth; air scenes; Rhine, Germany; Priory; Priory, seconds, 1969; MS024.007.074.00005 (Box 74)
    - Norway; unlabeled; Geneva, autumn; portraits; flowers; Tufts; Africa, mines; unlabeled, 1969; MS024.007.074.00006 (Box 74)
    - Conflans (commercial); 'slides to be duplicated'; portraits of Jean; Lenk, winter; Priory, special; Africa, super; visitors; Germany; garden rte, Cape Town; camp; Norway; mountains, meadows, trees; unlabeled; unlabeled, 1969; MS024.007.075.00001 (Box 75)
    - South America (commercial); campers; exotic; groups at Priory; travel; Annecy; Roussy de Sales; Annecy, cousin Imrie; unlabeled; loose slides, 1972; MS024.007.075.00002 (Box 75)
    - Africa; camp, Tornado; USA; portraits, visitors; Madiera; Riviera 1971; Riviera 1971; Riviera 1969; views of the Priory 1969, South America, MS024.007.075.00003 (Box 75)
    - Landscapes, Talloires; loose slides; Talloires; sewer; portraits; camp and unlabeled, 1950 -- 1960; MS024.007.075.00004 (Box 75)
      Slides
      MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
    - Loose slides; unlabeled; C. Raymond, A. Booth; flowers; Priory; visitors, 1950 -- 1970; MS024.007.075.00005 (Box 75)
      Slides.
    - Priory; homelife, Japan; Japan, schools, children; Japan; visitors to Priory; Japan, temples; Route to Paris, 1950 -- 1970; MS024.007.075.00006 (Box 75)
    - Campers watching the sun set over Lake Annecy, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03806; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      taken from MS024/007-071 - "Donald MacJannet slides from trips and Priory, ca. 1960-1980"
      People; Children; Views; Lakes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - A young camper at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03807; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Young campers in their swimming suits, 1962-10; MS024.007.DO.03808; Unknown (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Swimming; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Young children at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03809; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - A young MacJannet camper playing the guitar, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03810; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      taken from MS024/007-071 "Donald MacJannet slides from trips and Priory, ca. 1960-1980"
      People; Children; Instruments; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Campers gathered around the fire, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03811; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Staff; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - A meal at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03812; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Staff; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet among some young campers, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03813; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet Camp
    - MacJannet campers swimming in Lake Annecy, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03814; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - Young MacJannet campers, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03815; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet with Woody and Anita Woodworth and an unidentified woman in the United States, 1967-06; MS024.007.DO.03816; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      taken from MS024/007-072 - "Donald MacJannet slides from trips and home, ca. 1960-1980"
      People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Woodworth, Lynn "Woody"; Woodworth, Anita
    - Woody and Anita Woodworth photographed in the United States, 1967; MS024.007.DO.03817; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); Woodworth, Lynn "Woody"; Woodworth, Anita
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet with visitors to the Priory, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03818; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
    - MacJannet campers swimming in Lake Annecy, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03819; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      taken from MS024/007-072 - "Donald MacJannet slides from trips and home, ca. 1960-1975"
    - A group of MacJannet campers, 1963-08; MS024.007.DO.03820; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      taken from MS024/007-073 - "Donald MacJannet slides from travel and camp"
    - Young campers setting places at a table for a meal, 1962-09; MS024.007.DO.03821; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Dinners and Dining; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - MacJannet campers seated outside of a tipi (teepee) and dressed in Native American costumes, 1962-09; MS024.007.DO.03822; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Costumes; Buildings; Tipis; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Swimmers being applauded by other campers and visitors to Talloires, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03823; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      taken from MS024/007-073 - "Donald McJannet slides from travel and camp"
    - MacJannet campers picking wild flowers, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03824; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - Campers singing before a group of visitors at Talloires, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03825; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Staff; Children; Music and musical performances; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Campers enjoying a snack by Lake Annecy, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03826; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - A meal at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03827; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - Campers participate in a theater production at Talloires, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03828; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Theater; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - A theater production at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03829; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - Charlotte Blensdorf MacJannet addressing a group of campers while in costume, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03830; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Costumes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet Camp
    - Campers dressed in costumes at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03831; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Staff; Children; Costumes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Young boys at the MacJannet Camp with Lake Annecy in the background, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03832; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Lakes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - A young camper painting at camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03833; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - MacJannet campers during an outdoor activity, 1962-09; MS024.007.DO.03834; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - MacJannet campers in costume for an outdoor theater production during Parent's Day, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03835; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Costumes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - MacJannet campers and staff members, 1962-09; MS024.007.DO.03836; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - A young boy in costume at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03837; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - Swimming in Lake Annecy at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03838; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Staff; Children; Swimming; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - The bamboo "pipes (recorders)" made and used by children at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03839; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - MacJannet campers hiking in the mountains, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03841; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      taken from MS024/007-073 - Donald MacJannet slides from travel and camp"
    - Two dancers performing at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03842; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Dances and Dancing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - A MacJannet camper making a bamboo "pipe" or recorder, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03843; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - Roasting marshmallows "round the campfire" at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03844; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - MacJannet campers diving into Lake Annecy, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03845; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - Children during a sing-a-long at the MacJannet Camp, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03846; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - MacJannet campers climbing through the mountains, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03847; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - Sailing on Lake Annecy, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03848; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      Boats and boating; Sailing; Lakes; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - A group of young MacJannet campers in front of their cabin, 1962-09; MS024.007.DO.03849; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - MacJannet campers, 1963-08; MS024.007.DO.03850; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
    - MacJannet campers learning how to canoe from a staff member, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03851; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Staff; Children; Canoes and canoeing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - A row of MacJannet campers sitting on the dock, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03852; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Children; Swimming; Docks; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - A group of MacJannet campers during a meal outdoors, 1962; MS024.007.DO.03853; MacJannet, Donald (Box Shared 41)
      People; Staff; Children; Dinners and Dining; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Donald, Jean and Malcolm MacJannet, 1900; MS024.007.DO.04145 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Slides remain with Howard Cook's "Mr. Mac slideshow on occassion of memorial service" in MS024/007-071.
      Children; People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; Foster, Jean MacJannet; MacJannet, Malcolm
    - Appalachia Mountain Club hut master, 1912; MS024.007.DO.04146 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - Donald MacJannet swims in mile high Star Lake, Mt Madison, Appalachia Mountain Club, 1916; MS024.007.DO.04147 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Mountains; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; Appalachian Mountain Club
    - Donald MacJannet as a ranger, 1917; MS024.007.DO.04148 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - A young and happy pilot, Donald MacJannet (in middle), 1918; MS024.007.DO.04149 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; World War, 1914-1918; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - MacJannet School Chamonix ski party, 1926; MS024.007.DO.04150 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; Students; slide (photograph); MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Babe Ruth encourages a young MacJannet student, 1935; MS024.007.DO.04151 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Baseball; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Children; Students; People; slide (photograph); Ruth, Babe; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - MacJannet School students aid Armistice Day celebrations at the Arc de Triomphe, 1928; MS024.007.DO.04152 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Children; Students; slide (photograph); MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Donald and Jean MacJannet and friend in Germany, 1921; MS024.007.DO.04153 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; Foster, Jean MacJannet
    - MacJannet students visiting an airplane factory in 1927, MS024.007.DO.04154 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Students; Children; Airplanes; slide (photograph); MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - MacJannet School visit to battle fields, 1927; MS024.007.DO.04155 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Students; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - MacJannet pupils including Prince Philip, 1928; MS024.007.DO.04156 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Students; Children; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); Prince Philip, Duke of Edinburgh; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - Famous grey Ford with scout troopers in front of the MacJannet School, 1928; MS024.007.DO.04157 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Children; People; Students; Automobiles; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet School (The Elms)
    - MacJannet Camp, 1927; MS024.007.DO.04158 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Hiking with the MacJannet Camp, 1926; MS024.007.DO.04159 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Children; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet Camp
    - Donald MacJannet explaining the geography and geology of the Annecy region at camp, 1930; MS024.007.DO.04160 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet Camp
    - Anita and Woody Woodworth, 1965; MS024.007.DO.04161 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); Woodworth, Anita; Woodworth, Lynn "Woody"
    - MacJannet Camp tilting, 1960; MS024.007.DO.04162 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Canoes and canoeing; Children; slide (photograph); MacJannet Camp
    - Jean and Emory Foster on their wedding day, 1929; MS024.007.DO.04163 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); Foster, Jean MacJannet; Foster, Emory
    - Donald MacJannet teaching about air pressure, 1941; MS024.007.DO.04164 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Students; Children; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet School (Sun Valley)
    - Donald MacJannet goes off to ski, 1941; MS024.007.DO.04165 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - Skiing in Sun Valley with the MacJannet School, 1941; MS024.007.DO.04166 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Children; People; Skiing; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet School (Sun Valley)
    - Swimming with Donald MacJannet, Sun Valley, 1941; MS024.007.DO.04167 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Swimming; Children; Students; People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet School (Sun Valley)
    - Donald MacJannet (third from left in row second from bottom) and other campers and counselors of le Bourget camp, 1924; MS024.007.DO.04168 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; Children; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet at a masquerade ball, 1970; MS024.007.DO.04169 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - View of the Priory, 1970; MS024.007.DO.04170 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Buildings; slide (photograph)
    - Working to restore the Crypt Merieux of the Priory, 1975; MS024.007.DO.04171 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - Breidy Snyder, James Halsey and Jean MacJannet Foster at the Priory, 1975; MS024.007.DO.04172 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); Foster, Jean MacJannet
    - Planning meeting of the International Peace Academy at the Priory, 1975; MS024.007.DO.04173 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph)
    - A concert on the Priory lawn, 1975; MS024.007.DO.04174 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; Concerts; slide (photograph)
    - World Health Organization meeting participants on the lawn of the Priory, 1980; MS024.007.DO.04175 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); World Health Organization
    - A concert in the Priory, 1980; MS024.007.DO.04176 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Concerts; People; slide (photograph)
    - Charlotte (2nd from left) and Donald (3rd from right in back) MacJannet with a group at the Priory, 1970; MS024.007.DO.04177 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - Tea in the Priory garden after a concert, 1970; MS024.007.DO.04178 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - Breathing at the Priory, 1980; MS024.007.DO.04179 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - Visitors to the Priory in traditional Japanese dress, 1980; MS024.007.DO.04180 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - The Mount Holyoke chorus performing at the Priory, ca. 1975, MS024.007.DO.04181 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - The Mount Holyoke chorus descending the stairs of the Priory, 1975; MS024.007.DO.04182 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - Donald and Charlotte MacJannet with his life long friend Jim Halsey and Amos Booth and others, 1970; MS024.007.DO.04183 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Booth, Amos; Halsey, James H.
    - Bill Douglas and Donald MacJannet sharing a laugh on the shore of lake Annecy, 1975; MS024.007.DO.04184 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; Lakes; slide (photograph)
    - Jean Mayer, Donald MacJannet, Charlotte MacJannet, Dick Powell and Julia Halsey conduct a MacJannet Board meeting in the inner garden at the Priory, 1980; MS024.007.DO.04185 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross; Mayer, Jean; Halsey, Julia
    - Always a new interest for the MacJannets, 1970; MS024.007.DO.04186 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      People; Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; MacJannet, Donald Ross
    - MacJannet clan: Donald and Charlotte MacJannet with John McJannet and family, 1974; MS024.007.DO.04187 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf
    - Raymond Barr with Donald and Charlotte MacJannet at the Priory dedication ceremony, 1979; MS024.007.DO.04188 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
    - Jean Mayer speaks at the Priory dedication ceremony, 1979; MS024.007.DO.04189 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; Mayer, Jean; Tufts University
    - Donald MacJannet receiving his honorary doctorate degree from Tufts president Jean Mayer, 1979; MS024.007.DO.04190 (Box data_value_missing_242e21f306022fa9021eaf3082dcda3e)
      Donald and Charlotte MacJannet, papers; People; slide (photograph); MacJannet, Donald Ross; MacJannet, Charlotte Blensdorf; Mayer, Jean